{
    "target_configs": {
        "player": {
            "name": [
                "player_3_3SVDX1",
                "player_5_3SVDX1",
                "player_15_3SVDX1",
                "player_4_3SVDX1",
                "player_9_3SVDX1",
                "player_10_3SVDX1"
            ],
            "app_id": [
                3,
                5,
                15,
                4,
                9,
                10
            ],
            "animation": [
                "stand",
                "crouch",
                "liedown",
                "crouch",
                "crouch",
                "crouch"
            ],
            "feature_caption": [
                "A woman with medium skin, dark hair in a bun, wearing a dark V-neck shirt, light pants, and brown boots",
                "A female soldier wearing green tactical uniform, backpack, and black boots. Hair is tied back. She carries a utility vest and accessories.",
                "A bald man with medium skin, wearing a brown turtleneck, dark pants, and brown shoes.",
                "A woman with fair skin, wearing a white and blue shirt, blue pants, dark boots, a gray bandana, and a utility belt with pouches",
                "A man with medium skin tone, wearing a navy blue polo shirt, black pants, and blue shoes, with a dark watch on his wrist and black hair.",
                "A man with medium skin, wearing sunglasses, maroon polo shirt, beige pants, brown shoes, and a watch"
            ],
            "start_pos": [
                [
                    9534.697,
                    25843.106,
                    1333.053,
                    0,
                    -171.9269197604167,
                    0
                ],
                [
                    9879.883,
                    25772.285,
                    1322.04,
                    0,
                    -120.5548887921903,
                    0
                ],
                [
                    9951.997,
                    25808.2,
                    1321.588,
                    0,
                    57.47393240375408,
                    0
                ],
                [
                    9296.33,
                    25853.863,
                    1345.629,
                    0,
                    -175.70906851332964,
                    0
                ],
                [
                    9642.681,
                    25922.722,
                    1328.21,
                    0,
                    101.31243147163053,
                    0
                ],
                [
                    9239.967,
                    25911.825,
                    1349.687,
                    0,
                    -68.94939981866304,
                    0
                ]
            ],
            "type": [
                "None",
                "None",
                "None",
                "None",
                "None",
                "None"
            ]
        },
        "drone": {
            "name": [
                "drone_0_3SVDX1"
            ],
            "app_id": [
                0
            ],
            "animation": [
                "none"
            ],
            "feature_caption": [
                "Aerial drone with a black and white frame, dual rotors, and a streamlined design."
            ],
            "start_pos": [
                [
                    9439.102,
                    25773.09,
                    1537.756,
                    0,
                    46.14965052483697,
                    0
                ]
            ],
            "type": [
                "None"
            ]
        }
    },
    "sample_configs": {
        "sample_center": [
            9750.808,
            26105.256,
            1323.115
        ],
        "sample_radius": 746.882208730546
    },
    "refer_agents_category": [
        "player",
        "drone"
    ],
    "safe_start": [
        [
            8912.163,
            25924.425,
            1377.36,
            0,
            -7.25921405066254,
            0
        ],
        [
            9683.458,
            26710.872,
            1321.538,
            0,
            -97.47828780570859,
            0
        ],
        [
            9712.7,
            25146.882,
            1325.25,
            0,
            101.68216995134411,
            0
        ]
    ],
    "Questions": {
        "relative_distance": {
            "Question 1": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_woman_in_deep_V_top, the_man_in_blue_polo or the_man_in_burgundy_polo_and_light_pants?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_man_in_blue_polo",
                    "B. the_man_in_burgundy_polo_and_light_pants"
                ],
                "answer": "A. the_man_in_blue_polo"
            },
            "Question 2": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_woman_in_deep_V_top, White_Drone or the_woman_in_camo_vest?",
                "options": [
                    "A. White_Drone",
                    "B. the_woman_in_camo_vest"
                ],
                "answer": "A. White_Drone"
            },
            "Question 3": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_woman_in_deep_V_top, the_woman_in_floral_shirt or the_bald_man_in_brown_sweater_and_black_pants?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_woman_in_floral_shirt",
                    "B. the_bald_man_in_brown_sweater_and_black_pants"
                ],
                "answer": "A. the_woman_in_floral_shirt"
            },
            "Question 4": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_woman_in_camo_vest, the_woman_in_deep_V_top or the_bald_man_in_brown_sweater_and_black_pants?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_woman_in_deep_V_top",
                    "B. the_bald_man_in_brown_sweater_and_black_pants"
                ],
                "answer": "B. the_bald_man_in_brown_sweater_and_black_pants"
            },
            "Question 5": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_woman_in_camo_vest, White_Drone or the_man_in_burgundy_polo_and_light_pants?",
                "options": [
                    "A. White_Drone",
                    "B. the_man_in_burgundy_polo_and_light_pants"
                ],
                "answer": "A. White_Drone"
            },
            "Question 6": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_bald_man_in_brown_sweater_and_black_pants, the_woman_in_deep_V_top or the_man_in_blue_polo?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_woman_in_deep_V_top",
                    "B. the_man_in_blue_polo"
                ],
                "answer": "B. the_man_in_blue_polo"
            },
            "Question 7": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_bald_man_in_brown_sweater_and_black_pants, the_woman_in_camo_vest or White_Drone?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_woman_in_camo_vest",
                    "B. White_Drone"
                ],
                "answer": "A. the_woman_in_camo_vest"
            },
            "Question 8": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_woman_in_floral_shirt, the_woman_in_deep_V_top or the_man_in_burgundy_polo_and_light_pants?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_woman_in_deep_V_top",
                    "B. the_man_in_burgundy_polo_and_light_pants"
                ],
                "answer": "B. the_man_in_burgundy_polo_and_light_pants"
            }
        },
        "counting": {
            "Question 1": {
                "question": "How many individuals are observing something keenly in a crouch position?",
                "answer": "four"
            },
            "Question 2": {
                "question": "How many human figures are currently in a standing posture?",
                "answer": "one"
            },
            "Question 3": {
                "question": "How many women are present among the people in the scene?",
                "answer": "three"
            },
            "Question 4": {
                "question": "How many people in the scene have a bald head?",
                "answer": "one"
            },
            "Question 5": {
                "question": "What is the count of individuals who are wearing glasses?",
                "answer": "one"
            },
            "Question 6": {
                "question": "How many people in the scene are characterized by having black skin?",
                "answer": "two"
            },
            "Question 7": {
                "question": "Excluding the bald individual and anyone wearing glasses, how many people are present in the scene?",
                "answer": "four"
            },
            "Question 8": {
                "question": "What is the total count of human beings visible in the scene, regardless of their posture?",
                "answer": "six"
            }
        },
        "state": {
            "Question 1": {
                "question": "What's the state of the woman in the deep V-top?",
                "options": [
                    "A. stand",
                    "B. crouch",
                    "C. liedown",
                    "D. sit"
                ],
                "answer": "A. stand"
            },
            "Question 2": {
                "question": "What's the state of the woman in the camo vest?",
                "options": [
                    "A. stand",
                    "B. crouch",
                    "C. liedown",
                    "D. walk"
                ],
                "answer": "B. crouch"
            },
            "Question 3": {
                "question": "What's the state of the bald man?",
                "options": [
                    "A. stand",
                    "B. crouch",
                    "C. liedown",
                    "D. run"
                ],
                "answer": "C. liedown"
            },
            "Question 4": {
                "question": "What's the state of the woman in the floral shirt?",
                "options": [
                    "A. stand",
                    "B. crouch",
                    "C. liedown",
                    "D. jump"
                ],
                "answer": "B. crouch"
            },
            "Question 5": {
                "question": "What's the state of the man in the blue polo?",
                "options": [
                    "A. stand",
                    "B. crouch",
                    "C. liedown",
                    "D. others"
                ],
                "answer": "B. crouch"
            },
            "Question 6": {
                "question": "What's the state of the man in the burgundy polo?",
                "options": [
                    "A. stand",
                    "B. crouch",
                    "C. liedown",
                    "D. sit"
                ],
                "answer": "B. crouch"
            }
        },
        "relative_location": {
            "Question 1": {
                "question": "Where is the woman in the camo vest relative to the woman in the deep V top?",
                "options": [
                    "A. In front of",
                    "B. Behind",
                    "C. To the left of",
                    "D. To the right of"
                ],
                "answer": "A. In front of"
            },
            "Question 2": {
                "question": "Where is the woman in the floral shirt relative to the woman in the deep V top?",
                "options": [
                    "A. In front of",
                    "B. Behind",
                    "C. To the left of",
                    "D. To the right of"
                ],
                "answer": "B. Behind"
            },
            "Question 3": {
                "question": "Where is the man in the blue polo relative to the woman in the camo vest?",
                "options": [
                    "A. To the front-left of",
                    "B. To the back-right of",
                    "C. To the front-right of",
                    "D. To the back-left of"
                ],
                "answer": "B. To the back-right of"
            },
            "Question 4": {
                "question": "Where is the woman in the deep V top relative to the woman in the floral shirt?",
                "options": [
                    "A. Behind",
                    "B. In front of",
                    "C. To the left of",
                    "D. To the right of"
                ],
                "answer": "B. In front of"
            },
            "Question 5": {
                "question": "Where is the woman in the deep V top relative to the man in the blue polo?",
                "options": [
                    "A. To the front-right of",
                    "B. To the back-left of",
                    "C. To the front-left of",
                    "D. To the back-right of"
                ],
                "answer": "B. To the back-left of"
            },
            "Question 6": {
                "question": "Where is the woman in the camo vest relative to the man in the blue polo?",
                "options": [
                    "A. To the front-left of",
                    "B. To the back-right of",
                    "C. To the front-right of",
                    "D. To the back-left of"
                ],
                "answer": "A. To the front-left of"
            },
            "Question 7": {
                "question": "Where is the woman in the floral shirt relative to the man in the burgundy polo and light pants?",
                "options": [
                    "A. To the front-left of",
                    "B. To the back-right of",
                    "C. To the front-right of",
                    "D. To the back-left of"
                ],
                "answer": "A. To the front-left of"
            }
        }
    }
}